Preliminary Guide to the Public Policy Program records, 1973-1987 RG0118
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Public Policy Program records
1973-1987
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Public Policy Program
RG0118
2 Linear Feet 2 record center boxes
This collection contains correspondence, policies procedures, and exams. This material dates from 1973-1987.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1 is closed to research for 25 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Acquisition data is unknown.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Public Policy Program was part of the Graduate Institute of Public Policy, Education and Research.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, policies procedures, and exams. This material dates from 1973-87
Formerly ACC#55
Examinations; Working paper (George Washington University. Graduate Institute for Policy Education and Research); Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.)
- PhD Program Procedures and Policies, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Complete Set of GSAS Application Forms, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Doctoral Oral Exam Forms, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Education Policy Committee, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Education Policy Program, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Education Policy Students, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- EPOL Students Status, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Education Policy Seminar - 202, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Current Issues - Education - 202, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Topics in Education Policy - 222, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  General note
  Spring
- Topics in Education Policy - 222, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Fall
- Topics in Education Policy - 222, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Advanced Studies in Education - 290, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- EPOL 290, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dissertation Research - 399, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dissertation Research - 399, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- EPOL & PPOL Dissertation Research (399), 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Master Bibliography List, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Trustee Update, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American Work Force in the Eighties, By A. Adams, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Newsletter Descriptions, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Newsletter, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Anna Nelson - History in Public Policy, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Information on Robert Emmitt, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Journal of Human Resources, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Review of Economics and Statistics, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- JRB Assoc. Draft, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Saudi Arabia - World Bank, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Thomas Coleman, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Virginia Hodgkinson - Forward, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Seminar on Vocational Education: National Commission for Employment Policy, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Institute of Public Policy Studies, The University of Michigan, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Assn. for Public Policy Analysis and Management, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Chairment's Meeting Office of University and Summer Students, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Advanced Seminar on Policy Research, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Equipment, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Background Information for Cmte. to Dev, Public Policy Program, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- The New Educational Program in Pub. Policy: The First Decade, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Committee Retreat December 10 - 11 and Proposed Fields of Study, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Marketing Public Policy, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Education Policy 202, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Education Policy 202, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Education Policy 201, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Education Policy Brochure, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Resumes of Potential Faculty, 1979-1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Education Policy 201, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Education Policy 201, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Literature on Human Capital, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Committee to Develop a Doctoral Program In Public Policy, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Retreat (Annapolis), 12/10/1981-12/11/1981 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 12/1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 11/1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 10/1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 9/1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 8/1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 5/1986-7/1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 3/1986-4/1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1986-2/1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 12/1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 11/1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 9/1985-10/1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 7/1985-8/1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 5/1985-6/1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 4/1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1985-3/1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 7/1984-12/1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1984-6/1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 7/1983-12/1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1983-6/1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 5/1982-12/1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1982-4/1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 5/1981-12/1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1/1981-4/1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Correspondence - Arvil V. Adams, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Field Exams - Originals, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Comprehensive Exams - Fall 1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Comprehensive Exams - Psycology - Summer 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Comprehensive Exams - Sociolgy - Spring 1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Comprehensive Exams - Education - Spring 1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Old Syllabuses Education Policy, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Education Policy 222 Fall 1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Comprehesive Exam Education Policy, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- EPOL 290-10 Advanced Topics - EPOL, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- EPOL 290-10 Fall 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Comprehensive Exam Economics, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Comprehensive Exams Political Science, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)